<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GrandNapoleonSolitaireGame</string>

    <string name="title_activity_game">GameActivity</string>
    <string name="Start">Start</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="Normal_Difficulty">Normal Difficulty</string>
    <string name="Dummy_Difficulty">A Simple Example</string>
    <string name="No_Hint">Unable to find any good move</string>
    <string name="Win_Dialog">You win</string>

    <string name="about_info">Three generations of our family have been playing this solitaire for over 100 years. There are other Napoleon solitaires which can be found with a Google search, but this version is considered to be unique. While we believe it was played by Emperor Napoleon while exiled in Elba, but we cannot confirm this. It is intellectually demanding and not all dealt tableaus are solvable.   \n\n Professor Gerald Ratzer\n\n
                              Acknowledgement\n
                              This game is a McGill project. In addition to Professor Joseph Vybihal and Professor Gerald Ratzer, we would also like to thank Andrew Lin and Sok Heng Lim, the previous team that worked on this project.</string>
    <string name="title_home">About</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Instructions</string>
    <string name="instructions_info">- The game uses a standard deck of 52 cards.\n
                                     - The goal is to make 4 ordered stacks in the centre. The order can be either up or down, determined by the first card the player put in the middle.\n
                                     - Only the outermost cards can be moved.\n
                                     - Cards of same suit that are in sequence can be stacked. Unless the card is on the 5th row.\n
                                     - Player can put any card in the cellar or on any other empty rows.\n</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Gesture Support</string>
    <string name="gesture_support">Double Tap\n
                                   By double tapping an outer card, the card is moved to the middle stacks automatically if allowed by the rules.\n\n
                                   Auto Stack Move\n
                                   Stack of cards are always moved together, once user has moved the top card successfully, the subsequent cards will be moved automatically to the same destination.</string>
    <string name="game_rule">Game rule</string>
    <string name="grand_napoleon_solitaire">Grand Napoleon Solitaire</string>

</resources>
